Contact

lwolkovich@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lwolkovich (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Strategic Planning
Process Improvement
Negotiation

Languages Hebrew

Certifications
Registered Nurse

Elle Wolkovich

Registered Nurse Operating Room at HCA Central/West Texas Austin, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse in Surgical Services/Operating Room. Demonstrated history of working within both the health care setting as well as extensive background working within a corporate environment. Skills include: Operations management/planning, finance, and sales and customer relationship management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science in Nursing from The University of Texas at Austin.

Experience

HCA Central/West Texas Registered Nurse Operating Room September 2019 - Present (11 months)

Austin, Texas Area

Circulating RN for multiple locations in St. David's hospital system float pool with specialty lines in Cardiovascular, Orthopedic, Plastics and ENT, Neurological and Gynecological procedures.

Comprehensive Medical Services & Level II Trauma Center

St. David's Round Rock Medical Center is part of St. David's HealthCare, one of the largest health systems in Texas, which was recognized with a Malcolm Baldrige National Quality Award in 2014. With 171 beds, the hospital's comprehensive services include advanced cardiac care at the Heart Hospital of Austin at St. David's Round Rock—the first specialized cardiac facility in Williamson County—with the only Hybrid Operating Room (OR) in the county; as well as emergency services in a 24-hour emergency department, including advanced trauma care with a Level II Trauma Center; St. David's Urgent Care Round Rock; and St. David's Emergency Center in Cedar Park. St. David's Round Rock Medical Center is also known for providing advanced orthopedic and robotic services, among other complex specialties. In 2016, the hospital received the Distinguished Hospital Award for Clinical Excellence from

Healthgrades and also earned a national distinction for patient safety from The Leapfrog Group.

U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs RN Operating Room May 2019 - September 2019 (5 months) Dallas, Texas

Proud to serve those who served

Seton Healthcare Family
Registered Nurse Operating Room
February 2016 - April 2019 (3 years 3 months)
Seton Medical Center Austin

Austin's largest medical/surgical acute care center, Seton Medical Center Austin is the only hospital in Central Texas that performs heart transplants. One of four Magnet hospitals in the Seton Family of Hospitals, Seton Medical Center Austin offers comprehensive diagnostic and treatment services for both inpatients and outpatients and regional specialty programs including the Seton Heart Specialty Care and Transplant Center, Shivers Cancer Programs and the Marialice Shivers Regional Neonatal Center. Seton Medical Center Austin was also one of the first two hospitals in Texas to receive certification as a Primary Stroke Center.

This location also offers convenient and comprehensive 24-hour emergency health services for our neighbors in central Austin including SetonER.com for mini emergencies.

Seton Medical Center Austin is proud to announce our official redesignation by the American Nurses Credentialing Center as a Magnet hospital. Achieving Magnet redesignation requires satisfying a demanding set of criteria which measure the strength and quality of nursing and an interdisciplinary approach to patient care. It also sends a message to our community and our patients that we are committed to providing the best care possible.

ROUND2 INC., An Avnet Company
Executive Assistant
April 2011 - November 2012 (1 year 8 months)
Austin, TX

ROUND2 INC. is a leading eRecycling service provider offering a wide range of integrated asset disposition and technology recovery solutions.

ROUND2's revenue-based recycling services allow clients to better manage their end-of-life asset retirement process, technology rotation and data security requirements, while maximizing economic returns. ROUND2 is an R2 Certified, ISO 9001: 2008, ISO 14001: 2004, and OHSAS 18001: 2007 registered company. Find more information at www.round2.net.

SafeTScribe, LLC
Executive Assistant
December 2008 - October 2010 (1 year 11 months)

ClearCube Technology, Inc. Executive Assistant June 2004 - August 2007 (3 years 3 months)

Envision Creative Group
Executive Assistant
January 2003 - December 2005 (3 years)

Hotjobs Field Operations Manager 2002 - 2003 (1 year)

FiData Executive Assistant 2000 - 2001 (1 year)

Living.com Executive Assistant 1999 - 2000 (1 year)

Education

The University of Texas at Austin

Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing · (2016 - 2017)

Austin Community College
Associate of Applied Science, Nursing · (2014 - 2015)